Equal Love cross-live self-initiated staging meeting
Yay!
So we're going to have an equal love cross-live production meeting.
I'd like to have a meeting with the three of us.
Are you sure about this?
It's fine.
Can we decide?
Yes, we have the right to decide.
We'll be free to do as we please.
There you go.
Now that's delicious, isn't it?
Thank you very much.
Thank you... for those of you who don't know, but yes, I see. It's delicious now, isn't it? Thank you very much.
Still, you know, some of you who are watching this may not know,
What exactly is the Equal Love Cross Live?
Yes, that's right. First of all, I would like to explain.
Some of the fans are a little bit confused about it,
What kind of live show is it? So I'll give you a brief explanation,
So I'll give you a brief explanation: we'll be performing a full two hours of Korab songs.
Yes, it's a concert by Rico Love, so to speak.
On top of that, we're going to do a special cross-stage collaboration performance with a guest that you can only see at this concert! A cross stage?
Yes, that's right!
Surprisingly, many fans have the image of performing the whole show with the guests.
But we're going to have fun with the guests one song at a time.
So from here, we're going to do a cross-stage where you can perform one song with each of the guests at the Equal Love Cross Live.
We'd like you to think of a direction or project you'd like to do on the cross stage where you can perform one song, and we'd like you to present it to us.
Isn't this a big deal at all?
I wonder if it'll be okay if we're the directors.
Will it be okay?
I've put my name in the credits as director.
It'll be fine.
I'm fine.
So, without further ado, please...
I'll start with you, Noguchi-san.
On the first day, I'll be performing in collaboration with Kentomori-san.
I'd like to ask you for a favour.
I want to do a 247 dance collaboration.
That's great!
We collaborated on the show with Michael Jackson and Madonna's songs.
But since it's a cross live show, I thought it would be great if we could do a collaboration on a song from the show.
I thought 247 would be a good dance song, so I thought I'd say this one, how do you like it?
How do you like it?
It's great!
I didn't expect it to be so easy, but it's fine.
I'm going to propose a song for collaboration with the used.
What is it?
A live performance of Rainbow Rose.
Gorgeous!
You're hired!
Oh, no...
We haven't even decided yet.
It's still Ricola's cross-lab.
I think it'll be a real treat to perform what we've broadcast live.
I think it's a bit of a thrill.
Sayuka, Iori and Mayuka will sing in the broadcast.
And Annyong, Meanya, Shoko and Kiara danced.
There was a song...
I'd really like you all to see it.
What do you think?
Can I see Sayuka's back again?
May I? I'm already sounding like a nerd... a nerd! Can I dance while I watch? Can I look at Masayuka-san's back?
Boo-boo, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good.
It's really good, but speaking of Masaika-san, we made a show about him...
She wrote the lyrics to our graduation song, added melody to our beautiful lyrics, and performed an impromptu song.
It was really amazing.
It was so moving that I was moved to tears at the end.
There was a scene, so I'd be happy if you could perform it at the venue.
I'd be so happy! How about it?
Please do!
Enjoy! So...
I'm looking forward to it!
See you later, can I?
Yes, please.
And then, for the night show on the second day...
I'll be doing a cross collaboration with KENZA 3903.
Ta-da!
I want to do a rap version of Boysen Girl with everyone!
I want to do it!
Boyzun! Boyzun!
Boyz 'n' Girl can lick it!
Let's do it!
Let's do it, yeah, let's do it! Let's do it!
Poison Girl, it's everyone's, it's everyone's music!
I thought it would be great if we could collaborate with you and Kenza-san.
I'd like it if you could do the cross again.
Great, we're adopting it!
We're adopting all of them.
It'd be great if we could do Poison Poison together, it'd be fun and enjoyable!
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I'll have one too, please.
This is Hoi Jai-jan, a little rear Jai-jan before the cross-stage.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, can you come? I'd like you to come, I'd like each group to come.
And we'll do a collaboration and a collaboration performance together.
I've never done anything like this before.
I think it's a project that can only be done at a concert like this.
I'd like to do it again as a cross stage, different from the dialogue.
I'm so happy!
That's a lot of stuff!
Thank you very much!
Waikie, Miyajuri-san, please take care of us.
Thank you very much.
Yes, everybody, we're going to the tent line now.
Well, that was a really good planning meeting.
Hey!
Do you guys remember what I just said?
I have a whiteboard here.
I haven't written a single thing on it.
Hey, hey, hey.
We need one more initial.
Initial, initial.
You're the first.
I was an early.
MC and initial.
I'm sorry.
Thank you very much for ending so late... so sorry... a bit more...
Where's the fag?
Thank you very much.
You're late.
Well, now that we've got the ball rolling...
I have one more announcement.
What? What?
Two guests on the 21st, but one on the 22nd.
It hasn't been announced yet, has it?
Yes, that's right.
So there will be one more guest.
Oh, no!
Who is it?
Yay!
What do you think?
Yes, we've invited another guest for the evening performance on the 22nd.
But we can't announce it yet.
We'd like to invite that person we love so much to come.
Who?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Our favourite.
Wait, wait, wait, we're waiting.
And you two wait.
See you soon.
I'm looking forward to it.
Now that I've laughed
I hope you're all looking forward to the announcement.
Yes, ma'am.
So, once again, the evening performances on the 21st and 22nd will be
We'll be performing a full two hours of Equal Love songs
And we will also try our hand at the cross stage!
And for the daytime performance on the 22nd
We will be performing opposite not equal me and near equal joy.
We are looking forward to hearing from you!
Thank you very much!
That's all for now, this is Equal Love.
Bye-bye.